[{"id": 1488, "question": "Three-point-four billion riders on New York City subways and buses a year. This amazing number equals one-third of all mass transit trips in the United States. Ridership is at its highest in almost 60 years in almost every American city. A commuter advocacy group, \"Straphangers Campaign,\" attributes it to younger Americans, said Gene Russianoff. \"Millenials , those people born around the turn of the past century are much less car-oriented,\" he said. \"They are urban. They like not owning cars, they like less responsibility and there are a lot of them.\" In addition to millenials, many people believe public transit is economical and eco-friendly. In 2012 across America, people took 10.7 billion trips. \"When we talk about insurance rates going up, price of automobiles going up, then people are...\n\nQ: Which is Not the reason why the public is riding subways and buses in increasing numbers.", "options": ["Public transport facilities are better than before.", "Many people believe public transit is economical and eco-friendly.", "The system has gotten a lot more dependable.", "It is more convenient to ride city subways and buses."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 768, "question": "As shocking as the idea of baby birds growing up in a cigarette-filled home sounds, a new study suggests that some birds may benefit from putting the stuff from cigarette butts into their nests. The nicotine remaining in smoked filters may serve as a natural insecticide , driving harmful insects away from the nests and the baby birds living within. Tobacco plants produce nicotine because it defends against insects that would otherwise eat the plants. The butts are undoubtedly smelly. But birds are actually quite fond of smelly chemicals, such as those found in aromatic plants. Some nest-building species regularly fill their nests with fresh aromatics, possibly because the chemicals are good for the immune system or the development of the chicks. Alternatively, the plant chemicals might act...\n\nQ: What is the first experiment aimed at?", "options": ["Proving that heat traps attract harmful insects in Mexico City.", "Comparing smoked cigarette filters with unsmoked ones.", "Analyzing what is produced from smoked cigarette filters.", "Studying what it is that drives harmful insects away."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1672, "question": "In 1905, as part of his Special Theory of Relativity, Albert Einstein published the point that a large amount of energy could be released from a small amount of matter. This was expressed by the equation E = mc2. But bombs were not what Einstein had in mind when he published this equation. In 1929, he publicly declared that if a war broke out he would \"refuse to do war service, direct or indirect....\" His position would change in 1933, as the result of Adolf Hitler's coming into power in Germany. Einstein's greatest role in the invention of the atomic bomb was signing a letter to President Franklin Roosevelt urging that the bomb be built because some physicists feared that Germany might be working on an atomic bomb. Among those concerned were physicists Leo Szilard and Eugene Wigner. But t...\n\nQ: Please decide the order of the following events according to the passage.", "options": ["c,e,a,f,b,d", "a,e,b,d,f,c", "e,c,a,f,d,b", "e,c,b,f,a,d"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 958, "question": "Finally, I entered the university. Because of my careful savings, I did not have to work during the school year. Then, summer came and it was time to work harder than ever. I continued working as a waitress at night, instructed tennis camps several mornings a week and worked as a secretary for a few hours in the afternoons. I even decided to take a class at a community college. This class at the community college saved me $650. It was an extremely tiring summer and made me anxious to return to my relatively easy life at the university. During my second and third years of undergraduate schooling, I decided to work about five hours per week in the campus admissions office answering phones. This provided a little spending money and kept me from drawing my savings out. The overall situation lo...\n\nQ: Where did the writer probably work parttime before attending the university?", "options": ["In a restaurant.", "In the tennis camps.", "In a company.", "In the admissions office."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1648, "question": "One of my wonderful memories is about a Chrismas gift . Unlike other gifts,it came Wrap . On September 11th ,1958,Mum gave birth to Richard. After she brought him home from hospital,she put him in my lap ,saying,\"I promised you a gift ,and here it is.\" What an honor!I Turned four a month earlier and none of my friends had such a baby doll of their own.I played with It day and night .Isang to it .I told it stories .I told it over and over how much I loved it! One morning ,however,I found its bed empty. My doll was gone! Icried for it.Mum and Told me that the poor little thing bad been sent to a hospital. It had a fever. For several days I Heard Mum and Dad whispering such words as \"hopeless\",\"pitiful\",and \"dying\",which sounded Ominous. Chistmas was coming . \"Don't expect any present this ye...\n\nQ: Which word can best describe the feeling of the father when Christrmas was coming?", "options": ["Excitement.", "Happiness.", "Sadness.", "Disappointment."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 718, "question": "Alice's mother died when she was five. Although her brothers and sisters were loving and caring, their love couldn't take the place of a mother's. In 1925 Alice became my mother and told me that her family couldn't even afford her a doll. One afternoon in December 1982, when I was getting ready for Christmas, I suddenly decided to buy two dolls, one for my five-year-old daughter, Katie, and one for my old mother. Things went smoothly when a friend told me that his dad, who played Santa Claus in my area, would be willing to make a visit on Christmas morning to our home with the gifts! Knowing that my parents would also come to my house, I began to get ready for the most memorable day of my mother's life. Christmas Day arrived and so did Santa Claus at the planned time. Katie was very excite...\n\nQ: What did the friend's father do that Christmas morning?", "options": ["He acted as Santa Claus to send Christmas gifts.", "He went to her home to see Alice.", "He bought some Christmas gifts for Katie.", "He helped her to get Christmas gifts ready."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 910, "question": "Travel can be a lifesaver. But in today's economy with airlines adding new fees almost daily and ticket prices sharply on the rise, many have written off travel as too expensive. However, with a few saving tricks and a little research, there are still lots of great deals to be had on airline tickets and more. Early Bird Gets the Deal. Travel experts say that there are certain times of day when more deals are available. Airfares can change three times a day as airlines adjust their prices to fill up flights. Early morning is when the fares tend to be lowest.www.zxxk.com What Wouldn't a Business Traveler do? Flying when business travelers don't can save you big money. Most business travelers fly on Mondays and Fridays, so Tuesday and Wednesday are the best days. Airlines will usually lower t...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be filled in the blank in the text?", "options": ["Fly to popular places.", "Don't Miss the Holydays.", "Better Avoid the Crowds.", "Lose No Chance for Travelling."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2551, "question": "More than 4 in 10 cancers -- 600,000 in the UK alone -- could be prevented if people led healthier lives, say experts. The population of the UK is about 63,000,000. Latest figures from Cancer Research UK show smoking is the biggest avoidable risk factor , followed by unhealthy diets. The charity advises people to live healthily, limit alcohol intake and do regular exercise. According to the figures from 2007 to 2011, more than 300,000 cases of cancer recorded were linked to smoking. A further 145,000 were linked to unhealthy diets containing too much processed food. Obesity contributed to 88,000 cases and alcohol to 62,200. Sun damage to the skin and physical inactivity were also contributing factors. Professor Max Parkin, a Cancer Research UK statistician, says, \"There's now little doubt ...\n\nQ: According to Professor Max Parkin,   _  .", "options": ["it's OK to drink wine during festivals", "the causes of cancer are still unclear now", "unhealthy food should be completely banned", "a healthy lifestyle will protect us from cancer"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 582, "question": "Dear Ms Morris, We have come to know of an unfortunate incident you had with our customer service department and we would like to deeply apologize for the inconvenience caused to you by the customer service manager's behavior. We have noted down your complaint (number 797329SA) and would like to let you know that strict action will be taken against the employee. He is a new employee with little experience and so his attitude towards his job was over enthusiastic and he lacked proper judgment. We are by no means excusing his behavior but I would like to request you not to take any legal action against the company as we are very sorry for what happened. To express our appreciation, please accept the offer of free servicing of all products of our company that you own for up to three years. We...\n\nQ: Which is most likely to happen according to the first letter?", "options": ["The new employee will be punished.", "Ms Morris will get her air conditioner repaired.", "Nate Borges will take legal action against Ms Morris.", "Ms Morris will get all products of the company for free."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3401, "question": "One of the best-known American writers of children's books is Alfred Strong, or Doctor Strong, as he is better known to readers everywhere. Now, an art show called \"Doctor Strong From Then to Now\" is travelling around the United States. The pictures and drawings show the history of Doctor Strong. Doctor Strong first became famous almost fifty years ago when his first children's book was published. Since then, he has written forty-five books that have sold more than one hundred million copies around the world. Doctor Strong's books are known for their easy use of words and colorful, hand-drawn pictures. These drawings bring life to his imaginary creatures. The Cat in the Hat, Horton the Elephant, The Grinch Who Stole Christmas, and hundreds of others. The San Diego Museum, in California, or...\n\nQ: Doctor Strong first became famous in   _  .", "options": ["his eighties when an art show was travelling around the United States", "his fifties when his drawings and writings were published", "nineteen eighty-four when his book MeEligot's Pool was published", "his thirties when his first book was published"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2602, "question": "Eighteen-year-old Dana Kiger is happily running after balls on the soccer field. But not long ago, she couldn't remember her love of the game, her parents' faces or even her name. At 16, the Tennessee honor student and star athlete was hit from behind while playing in a soccer game. She fell to the ground, her head striking the hard ground. The blow knocked out nearly all of Kiger's memories. With no physical injury or unusual change in her brain, doctors thought Kiger's memory would return in a few days. But it did not. And two and a half years later, it still hasn't. Kiger--who has no memory of her family, her childhood or her life before her injury--has had to create new memories, restart relationships and relearn old skills. \"The only thing I had ...I could walk, write, but I didn't kn...\n\nQ: According to the doctors, the case of Kiger is  _  .", "options": ["natural", "frightening", "surprising", "common"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3095, "question": "The U.S. Department of Labor statistics show that there is an oversupply of college trained workers and that this oversupply is increasing. Already there have been more than enough teachers, engineers, physicists, aerospace experts, and other specialists. Yet colleges and graduate schools continue every year to turn out highly trained people to compete for jobs that aren't there. The result is that graduates cannot enter the professions for which they were trained and must take temporary jobs which do not require a college degree. On the other hand, there is a great need for skilled workers of all sorts: carpenters, electricians, mechanics, plumbers, TV repairmen. These people have more work than they can deal with, and their annual incomes are often higher than those of college graduates....\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT a reason why college enrollments go up every year?", "options": ["Many people believe that the only way to success is a college education.", "Many parents want their children to go to college.", "High school teachers urge their students to go to college.", "Every young man and woman wants to go to college."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3360, "question": "\"Hitler and the Germans,\" an exhibition in Berlin's German Historical Museum which aims to investigate the society that created Hitler, has seen more than 10,000 visitors walk through its doors since opening on Friday. Rudolf Trabold, a spokesman for the museum, said there were 4,000 visitors to the exhibition on the first day alone. People visiting the exhibition said they had waited as long as one and a half hours to get in. Ravi Nair, a 73-year-old Indian visitor, said: \"I had to queue for about an hour but it was worth it. The exhibition should help people in democratic countries realize that their vote is very valuable.\" Trabold said \"Hitler and the Germans\" was so popular because it was the first exhibition to explain how a man who lived on the margins of society for 30 years, in Vie...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["People have different attitudes to \"Hitler and the Germans\".", "\"Hitler and the Germans\" attracts plenty of people.", "What effect \"Hitler and the Germans\" has on history.", "What people should learn from \"Hitler and the Germans\"."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1129, "question": "The U. S. Postal Service (USPS) is losing billions of dollars a year. The government company that delivers \"small mail\" is losing out to email and other types of electronic communication. First-class mail amount fell from a high point of 104 million pieces in 2000 to just 64 million pieces by 2014. Congress permits the 600.000-empIoyee USPS to hold a monopoly over first-class and standard mail. The company pays no federal, state or local taxes; pays no vehicle fees; and is free from many regulations on other businesses. Despite these advantages, the USPS has lost $52 billion since 2007, and will continue losing money without major reforms. The problem is that Congress is preventing the USPS from reducing costs as its sales decline, and is blocking efforts to end Saturday service and close ...\n\nQ: The author probably that the USPS   _  .", "options": ["needs government's protection as ever", "can work together with other businesses", "must be replaced by international companies", "should be sold out and become a private service"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2105, "question": "Believe it or not, there're always some people who like staying up too late. However, sleeping early can bring us many benefits. 1. Healthy heart. Staying up late in the night is a way to hurt your body with high blood pressure and cholesterol . These are the risks associated with the heart. 2. Reduce stress. A peaceful sleep in the night relieves physical and mental stress. It relaxes the body and mind. With insufficient sleep you're risking your health with heart attacks and other diseases. 3. Improve memory. Sleeping early lets your mind arrange the thoughts well. Waking up early with a fresh mind will regain all of it. 4. Protect you from diseases. By sleeping late in the night you're only stressing yourself, which will increase the blood pressure and cholesterol levels. So sleep early...\n\nQ: What will happen if you sleep less than seven hours?", "options": ["Losing weight.", "Becoming sleepless.", "Becoming active", "Becoming fat."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3299, "question": "Do you feel embarrassed when your mum tries to use slang or when she calls you by your childhood nickname in front of your friends? And how about searching for the nearest exit when your father dances with joy when he finds his favorite CD in the shop? Loving them dearly doesn't prevent you from feeling uncomfortable around them. And parents have to accept that Adam Gopnick, a writer for the New Yorker magazine, said in an article published by the BBC: ''The one thing that is written into the human genome is that exactly at the age of 13, your child... will discover that you are now the most embarrassing, ridiculous and annoying person on the planet.'' A survey by the site YoungPoll.com in 2010 suggested that one in three youngsters is so _ by their parents that they refuse to be seen with...\n\nQ: What does William Blake's comment suggest?", "options": ["His father had learnt a lot about parenting when he was 21.", "His father changed a lot since he was 21.", "He began to appreciate his father when he was 21.", "His father stopped doing the embarrassing things to him."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 441, "question": "You could feel sorry for Alberto Torres, who is blind. The last thing he remembers seeing was his daughter being born 13 years ago. Then the world went blank; he can only imagine what his only child looks like now, as a teenaged honor student. Bad luck is no stranger to this warm and thoughtful 37-year-old man. His mother died of cancer when he was 4, and his father, who was often ill, had to give him up to the care of the state when he was 11. He later worked for 19 years in a workshop making household goods, deathly boring work. Earlier this month, Alberto Torres's wife, who had just been laid off from her job, had to have a breast removed due to cancer and now faces a year of radiation treatments. Things seemed always to go from almost incredibly bad to worse. Even Mr. Torres's good luc...\n\nQ: What is the principle of the hospital in employing a worker?", "options": ["Sympathy counts most.", "Ability comes first.", "Preference for the blind.", "Easy job for the weak."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2577, "question": "Have you ever heard the saying \" _ \"? Here is how a new teacher made friends with the girls and boys in her class on the first day of school. As the bell rang, the teacher smiled at each girl and boy. Then she said in a quiet voice, \"Good morning. How nice it is to have all of you in my class this year. I'd like to know each of you. I am sure we will enjoy working together.\" Everyone felt that she meant what she said because of her sweet voice and her friendly look. She told the girls and boys her name and wrote it on the blackboard. Then she told them some of the things she liked to do and she was hoping to do with them during the year. Then she said to the class, \"Now you know my name and the things I like and I want to know your names and the things you like. Then I will feel that I kno...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["How to Make Friends", "Teachers Can Make Friends with Students", "A Friend in Need Is a Friend Indeed", "How to Be Friends with New Comers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3332, "question": "Trees should only be pruned when there is a good and clear reason for doing so and , fortunately, the number of such reasons is small. First, pruning may be done to make sure that trees have a desired shape or size.The object may be to get a tree of the right height, and at the same time to help the growth of small side branches which will thicken its appearance or give it a special shape.Secondly, pruning may be done to make the tree healthier.You may cut diseased or dead wood, or branches that are rubbing against each other and thus cause wounds.The health of a tree may be encouraged by removing branches that are blocking up the centre and so preventing the free movement of air. One result of pruning is that an open wound is left on the tree and this provides an easy entry for disease, b...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["The history of tree pruning.", "The reasons for tree pruning.", "Some directions for tree pruning.", "Some results of tree pruning."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 75, "question": "Some people collect stamps. Other people collect works of art or musical instruments. But a man in the American state of Maryland collects secrets. For the past 10 years, people have been sending Frank Warren postcards and other objects with secrets written on them. He now has a million secrets. \"It's a drawing of a lift. And the secret says: 'I feel guilty when I take lifts for one floor, so I limp when I get out.'\" Frank said. Ten years ago, Mr. Warren created an art project called PostSecret. People then began to send him postcards, other objects and emails telling their secrets. Every Sunday, he chooses 10 secrets and puts them on the website. Mr. Warren says he created PostSecret so people could share their secrets in a safe place. \"I was struggling with secrets in my own life. And it...\n\nQ: What do we know about Eric Perry from the passage?", "options": ["His family are eager to collect the books written by Frank.", "His main job is to deliver mails and postcards for Frank.", "He has been a postman who has a great many secrets.", "He has developed a good relationship with Frank."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1036, "question": "There are 132 rooms, 32 bathrooms, and 6 floors to accommodate all the people who live in, work in, and visit the White House. There are also 412 doors, 147 windows, 28 fireplaces, 7 staircases, and 3 lifts. At various times in history, the White House has been known as the \"President's Palace\", the \"President's House\", and the \"Executive Mansion\". President Theodore Roosevelt officially gave the White House its current name in 1901. The White House receives approximately 6,000 visitors a day. With five full-time chefs, the White House kitchen is able to serve as many as 140 guests and hors d'oeuvres to more than 1,000 people. The White House requires 570 gallons of paint to cover its outside surface. For recreation, the White House has a variety of facilities available to people who live ...\n\nQ: In normal cases, how many people visit the White House per day?", "options": ["1,000.", "6,000.", "140.", "570."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 377, "question": "Two thieves came to a house to steal something. They dug a hole in the wall of the house. There lived many mice in the house. The woman in the house saw a mouse crawl into the house in the moonlight. \"Look! In comes one,\" she said to the man in the house. The thief was so frightened that he hurriedly crawled out of the house and said to the one waiting outside, \"She found me when I was just in.\" But the thief outside didn't believe him, so he said, \"Let us try to crawl into the house together.\" At that time two mice happened to crawl into the house, too. The woman saw the mice and shouted, \"In come two, catch them!\" The two thieves were terribly frightened. The man in the house said, \"You saw them come in but where are they? I will catch them tonight.\" The two thieves started running away ...\n\nQ: The two thieves failed to steal anything from the house because   _  .", "options": ["they were found out", "they were frightened by what they had heard in the house", "they didn't work together well with each other", "mice stopped them from doing so"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 8, "question": "Little Tommy was doing very badly in math. His parents had tried everything--tutors, cards, special learning centers--in short, everything they could think of. Finally they took Tommy to a catholic school. After the first day, little Tommy came home with a very serious look on his face. He didn't kiss his mother hello. Instead, he went straight to his room and started studying. Books and papers were spread out all over the room and little Tommy was hard at work. His mother was surprised. She called him down to dinner and as soon as he finished eating, he went back to his room, without a word. In no time he was back hitting the books as hard as before. This went on for some time, day after day while the mother tried to understand what was happening. Finally, little Tommy brought home his re...\n\nQ: The last sentence in the passage shows that  _  .", "options": ["Tommy felt sorry for the man", "Tommy was afraid of being nailed", "Tommy didn't like the plus sign", "Tommy liked playing jokes on others"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2049, "question": "It was just three degrees above zero. \"That's cold,\" thought Jane as she got ready to deliver her morning papers. Jane has 50 customers, and on cold mornings when she couldn't ride her bike, it took her more than an hour to make her rounds. As she collected her papers and put them into a big canvas bag, Jane regretted that she hadn't finished her math homework the night before. There was still time. She'd hurry with the papers and finish the math before breakfast. Less than an hour later, Jane was nearly finished. She had only five customers to go. She could then head for home to complete her math while her mom fixed breakfast. As she rounded the corner, she saw a car in the middle of the street. It was Mr. Zimmerman, the elderly man who walked with a walking stick. His car was out of gas....\n\nQ: Mr. Zimmerman was old and   _  .", "options": ["couldn't drive well", "would have nobody to help him", "was not rich enough to buy gas", "was not able to walk a long way"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 308, "question": "When we say older people shrink, we don't mean they become tiny enough to fit in your pocket! We just mean that it's common for older people to become a little shorter over time. This kind of shrinking can't be reversed, although people can slow or stop this process. But why does shrinking happen at all? Because of gravity (the force that keeps your feet on the ground) , cushions between the bones in the spine , get compressed , which makes a person lose a little height and become shorter. Another reason why some older people shrink is because of osteoporosis . Osteoporosis occurs when bone is broken down and not enough new bone material is made. Over time, bone is said to be lost because it's not being replaced. Bones become smaller and weaker and can easily break if someone with osteopor...\n\nQ: What should we do if we don't want to shrink faster?", "options": ["We should try to reduce gravity.", "We should be careful not to be hurt by others.", "We should sleep as long as possible.", "We should keep away from smoking and drinking alcohol."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2769, "question": "Hurricane reached the northeastern United States today and caused death and destruction everywhere. The killer storm carried winds of 135 miles per hour. The high winds and heavy rains created extremely dangerous waves. It is not yet known how many people died or were hurt in this storm, but it is said that the numbers will be very high. With the arrival of the tornado season, the National Weather Service is again telling people how to protect themselves from these deadly storms. The winds from tornadoes are the most violent winds on earth. They can blow up to 400 miles per hour. A _ looks like a funnel . It is also very loud. It may sound like a train coming at you. In fact, the winds from a tornado can pick up a train and throw it around. If a tornado is seen in your area, it is very imp...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passages that   _  .", "options": ["nobody tried to help the local people", "hurricane damaged the northwestern coast of US", "when there is flooding, sandbags can be made and used to build walls", "people are often taught how to protect themselves from snowstorms"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2220, "question": "Davey wanted to play baseball. But fifty years ago, in his small town, he couldn't find enough players for two full teams or an empty lot big enough for a field. And when he played ball in his back yard, he just broke windows and got into trouble. So Davey began playing with a plastic golf ball and a broom handle for a bat. When his dad, David Mullaney, a former semi-pro baseball pitcher , realized his son was hurting his arm trying to throw curves with the little plastic ball, he decided to find a better solution. Mullaney got a bunch of hollow plastic _ from a local factory, sat down at his kitchen table and began cutting different size holes in the balls with a razor knife. He thought maybe the holes would alter the ball's flight and help his son throw curves and sliders without hurting...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us something about  _  .", "options": ["Davey, a famous baseball player", "a popular ball game in the 1950's", "the birth of Wiffle ball", "the success of a family business"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1996, "question": "When Carlos Westez died at the age of 76, a language died, too. Westez, more commonly known as Red Thunder Cloud, was the last speaker of the Native American language, Catawba.www.ks5u.com Anyone who wants to hear various songs of the Catawba tribe can get in touch with the Smithsonian Institution in Washington, D.C., where, back in the 1940s, Red Thunder Cloud recorded a series of songs for future generations. They are all that is left of the Catawba language. The language that people used to speak is gone forever. We are all aware of the damage that modern industry can do to the world's ecology. However, few people are aware of the effect that widely spoken languages have on other languages and ways of life. English has spread all over the world. Chinese, Spanish, Russian, and Hindi have...\n\nQ: Which of the following led to the disappearance of Catawba?", "options": ["Widely spoken languages.", "Ways of life.", "Population control.", "Modern industry."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2615, "question": "What is it: Work & Travel USA Who are qualified: Fulltime college students, above 18 years old About the program: Application for the 2009 Work & Travel USA program has just started. It's an 8~16 weeks' summer program for college students to work and travel in the U.S.. Employers include Boeing, Hilton Hotel and 7Eleven. For next summer, about 3,500 positions are open to Chinese students. Applicants must pass a language test and sometimes an interview, and pay a registration fee to join the program. (source : www. Cultureexchange. org) _ What is it: Shanghai Volkswagen jobs Who are qualified: College students graduating in 2009 About it: Shanghai VW offers over 300 positions from engineering to marketing to college students graduating in 2009. Applicants should have an excellent academic r...\n\nQ: These advertisements are most probably advertisements   _  .", "options": ["on the Internet intended for the general public to read", "in a newspaper intended for large companies to read", "on the Internet intended for college students to read", "in a newspaper intended for college students to read"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2407, "question": "Wang Lu, 24, one of many students studying abroad who'll come home for work, majors in business & management studies at Edinburgh's Napier University. She had planned what to do after graduation in the UK: two years' work experience at a restaurant and a tour around Europe. But now her plans are up in the air. Following the UK Home Secretary's meeting on reform of the student immigration system, the UK government recently announced the end of the post-study work visa from April 2012. This will force tens of thousands of Chinese students to leave the UK after graduation. Sadly, the domestic job market doesn't welcome them with open arms. A report by Tigtag.com at the end of 2011 showed that over 35 percent of students admitted that they have employment problems. \"Returning students often ha...\n\nQ: Why is Wang Lu forced to leave the UK after graduation?", "options": ["Because post-study work visa will come to an end.", "Because she has no effective ways to learn English.", "Because there are no majors that suit her in Britain.", "Because different work practices worry employers."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3467, "question": "My father was poor in expressing his feelings. I knew that my dad loved me, but showed me love in other ways. There was one particular time in my life when this became real to me. I always believed that my parents had a good marriage, but gradually the strain on my mom and dad's relationship was quite evident. However, I was not prepared for the day when Dad had decided to leave. All that I could think of was that I was going to become a product of a divorced family. I kept telling myself that it wasn't going to happen. The night before he left, I stayed up in my room for a long time. I prayed and I cried and I wrote a long letter to my dad. I told him how much I loved him and that I would always and forever be his Krissie. As I folded my note, I stuck in a picture of me with a saying I ha...\n\nQ: Why did the author's father decide to leave?", "options": ["Because he was poor in showing his feelings.", "Because his wife was always giving orders.", "Because serious problems occurred in their marriage.", "Because the strain on father-daughter relationship was evident."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1161, "question": "Though I have traveled in hundreds of trains, few unusual things have ever happened to me. But one day in a train something did happen. I do not mean that I was hurt: no one was hurt. I do my work in a hot country far away from England. Every September I go there to do my business, and every July I come back to England to have a rest. So every September I go to Paris and take a train from the great French city to Mendova, and at Mendova I catch my ship. There is one very fast train from Paris to Mendova, and it suits me well. It goes as far as Endoran, but it stops at Mendova for a few minutes to let travelers get out or in. It is called The Flying Bluebird. It reaches Mendova at seven minutes past nine in the morning, and it is never late. A ship leaves Mendova at half past eleven, and so...\n\nQ: It can be learned from Para.10 that the author was afraid that   _  .", "options": ["he would have to spend another sleepless night on the train", "more people might crowd into the train", "he would miss the ship that went where he worked", "he would have to buy another ticket"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2047, "question": "When a child is told he is \"uncool\", it can be very painful. He may say he doesn't care, and even act in ways that are opposite of cool on purpose. But ultimately, these are simply ways to handle sadness by pretending it's not there. Helping a child feel better in school had to be careful. If you say, \"Why are you worried about what other children think about you? It doesn't matter!\" Children know that it does matter. Instead, an active way may be best. You could say, \"I'm going to do a couple of things for you to help you feel better in school.\" If a boy is having trouble making friends, the teacher can help him. The teacher can arrange things so that he has chances to use his abilities to contribute to class projects. This is how the other children learn how to value his good qualities a...\n\nQ: The passage mainly talks about   _  .", "options": ["how to help an unpopular child", "why some children are unpopular", "who is responsible for unpopular children", "how to find out good points of unpopular children"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 884, "question": "There's a widespread perception in the United States that a university degree is the key to success. But a growing number of educators now say there are other possibilities, especially for students who might not succeed at university level. This is not a traditional classroom. At the apprentice program run by the Plumbers and Steamfitters Union in the state of Maryland, Travis Strawderman and other students make money while they learn. \"I \\t's completely changed my life around,\" he said. \"I've been able to pay off all my debts. I can say I'm actually responsible enough to have my own family.\" Strawderman's five-year program teaches him technical skills free of charge. He says he considered university, but it didn't interest him. Economics Professor Robert Lerman says Strawderman is not alo...\n\nQ: Where does Travis Strawderman learn?", "options": ["In a university.", "In a traditional classroom", "At an apprentice program.", "In a high school"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1008, "question": "No matter where you travel in Asia, you'll find yourself faced with a new culture. You can start your Asian exploration by visiting some of these attractive cities first. Beijing, China Beijing is the second largest city in China and serves as the capital. The city is so old, in fact, that almost every building has some sort of cultural or historic features -- no matter how small. Getting around the city you'll find yourself faced with amazing temples , the largest palaces in the world, and many works of art that leave you breathless. Siem Reap, Cambodia Siem Reap is the capital city of Siem Reap Province in northwestern Cambodia. Siem Reap has a lot of French and Chinese-style architectures. In the city, there are traditional dance performances, silk farms, fishing villages and a bird san...\n\nQ: The writer's purpose in writing the passage is   _  .", "options": ["to introduce several attractive cities in Asia", "to compare some tourist cities in Asia", "to tell readers not to visit European cities", "to write an advertisement about a travel company"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1563, "question": "Two things changed my life: my mother and a white plastic bike basket. I have thought long and hard about it and it's true. I would be a different person if my mom hadn't turned a silly bicycle accessory into a life lesson I carry with me today. My mother and father were united in their way of raising children, but it mostly fell to my mother to actually carry it out. Looking back, I honestly don't know how she did it. Managing the family budget must have been a very hard task., but she made it look effortless. If we complained about not having what another kid did, we'd hear something like, \"I don't care what so -and -so got for his birthday, you are not getting a TV in your room a car for your birthday a lsvish sweet 16 party.\" We had to earn our allowance by doing chores around the hous...\n\nQ: To the author, it seemed to be a horrible turn of events that", "options": ["something spoiled her paying plan", "the basket cost more than she had saved", "a neighborhood girl had bought a new bike", "someone else had got a basket of the same kind"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2772, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time....\n\nQ: Among all the characters mentioned in the passage, who directed films in Hollywood?", "options": ["Roland Emmerich.", "Tom and Summer.", "Burt and Verona.", "Esther."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2434, "question": "May 28 (Reuters Life!) - A Japanese university is giving away Apple Inc's (AAPL.O) trendy iPhone to students for free, but with a catch: the device will be used to check their attendance. The project, which is being tested ahead of its formal launch in June, involves 550 first and second year students and some staff of a department at Aoyama Gakuin University, which is located just outside Tokyo in Sagamihara city. The school's iPhones are meant to create a mobile information network between students and professors, but they are also a convenient way for the teachers to take attendance in class. As students enter the room, instead of writing their name on a sheet, they simply type in their ID number and a specific class number into an iPhone application. To prevent students from logging in...\n\nQ: The iphone being tested at Aoyama Gakuin University is mainly to   _", "options": ["help students to study hard", "check students' attendance", "help learn the information network", "develop a special classroom"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1422, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud.Your card information can even be on sale on an illegal website.Websites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care.Online shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they had bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number--or sell the information over the Internet.Computer hackers have broken down security system, raising questions about the safety of card holder information. Several months ago, 25,000 customers of a CD universe, an online music retailer , were not lucky.Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Website after the retailer refused to pay $ 157,828 to get back the information.Credit-card firms are now fighting again...\n\nQ: Thieves usually get the information of the credit-card   _  .", "options": ["because many customers lost their cards", "by paying money for people working in the information companies", "because of the carelessness of the customers", "by stealing the information from Websites"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1, "question": "The rain had continued for a week and the flood had created a big river which were running by Nancy Brown's farm. As she tried to gather her cows to a higher ground, she slipped and hit her head on a fallen tree trunk. The fall made her unconscious for a moment or two. When she came to, Lizzie, one of her oldest and favorite cows, was licking her face. At that time, the water level on the farm was still rising. Nancy gathered all her strength to get up and began walking slowly with Lizzie. The rain had become much heavier, and the water in the field was now waist high. Nancy's pace got slower and slower because she felt a great pain in her head. Finally, all she could do was to throw her arm around Lizzie's neck and try to hang on. About 20 minutes later, Lizzie managed to pull herself and...\n\nQ: The following are true according to the passage except  _  .", "options": ["It took Lizzie and Nancy about 20 minutes to get to safety.", "It was raining harder when Nancy managed to get up.", "The bad weather made it difficult for rescuers to find Nancy.", "Nancy took hold of the rope and climbed into the helicopter."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 639, "question": "The Healthy Habits Survey shows that only about one third of American seniors have correct habits.Here are some findings and expert advice. 1.How many times did you brush your teeth yesterday? *Finding:A full 33% of seniors brush their teeth only once a day. *Step:Remove the 300 types of bacteria in your mouth each morning with a batteryoperated toothbrush.Brush gently for 2 minutes,at least twice a day. 2.How many times did you wash your hands or bathe yesterday? *Finding:Seniors,on average,bathe fewer than 3 days a week.And nearly 30%wash their hands only 4 times a day-half of the number doctors recommend. *Step:We touch our faces around 3,000 times a day-often inviting germs to enter our mouth,nose,and eyes.Use toilet paper to avoid touching the door handle.And,most important,wash your ...\n\nQ: What is found out about American seniors?", "options": ["Most of them have good habits.", "Nearly 30% of them bathe three days a week.", "All of them are fighting germs better than expected.", "About one third of them brush their teeth only once a day."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2018, "question": "If you are thinking of putting your child in a private high school instead of a public one, you should do some research. You will find that most private schools offer some advantages. One of the most important details of a good high school is small class size. Many public schools might have 30 or even 35 students in each class. However, many private schools limit the size to about 15 to 20 kids per class. This is a good thing because it allows each teacher to offer every student more attention. Another thing to mention is the interesting classes. For example, while the typical high school might only offer Spanish and French as foreign languages, private schools often have several other languages to choose from. This is especially important if your child is actually interested in studying a...\n\nQ: By writing this text, the author is probably encouraging parents to   _  .", "options": ["pay attention to their children's study", "appreciate the advantages of public schools", "help their children choose right colleges", "send their children to private high schools"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2385, "question": "International Schools Services Experience teaching overseas Have you thought of working overseas? International Schools Services is looking for teachers for thousands of positions.Schools are looking for experienced, well-trained persons who must meet two of the three criteria: *A four-year bachelor's degree *Certification in a subject *Two years' successful teaching experience in a public or private school Attend one of our International Recruitment Conferences .Hundreds of schools will be available.Over 2,000 positions are expected to be filled. *Atlanta--December 4,201 1--December 6, 2011 *Bangkok--January 4, 2012~January 7, 2012 *Boston--February 5, 2012~February 9, 2012 *San Francisco--February 13, 2012~February 16, 2012 Becoming an international educator will offer you a journey you ...\n\nQ: If Mike has free time from February 6 to 8, which city would he fly to for a recruitment conference?", "options": ["Atlanta.", "Bangkok.", "Boston.", "San Francisco."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2742, "question": "Occasionally, my father came back drunk. Late at night, he beat on the door, pleading to my mother to open it .He was on his way home from drinking, gambling, or some combination thereof, misspending money that we could have used and wasting time that we desperately needed. It was the late-1970s. My parents were separated. My mother was now raising a group of boys on her own. My father spouted off about what he planned to do for us, buy for us.In fact, he had no intention of doing anything. As a father who was supposed to love us, in fact, he lacked the understanding of what it truly meant to love a child--or to hurt one. To him, this was a harmless game that kept us excited and begging. In fact, it was a cruel, corrosive lie. I lost faith in his words and in him. I wanted to stop caring, ...\n\nQ: The writer used not to feel Father's true love because  _   .", "options": ["father showed his love but had no good way to express himself to his children", "he just lost himself in his own mind without getting close to his father", "father was too busy so unable to communicate with his children enough", "he had a prejudice and was too stubborn to feel it"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 526, "question": "Runners in a relay race pass a stick in one direction. However, merchants passed silk, gold, fruit, and glass along the Silk Road in more than one direction. They earned their living by traveling the famous Silk Road. The Silk Road was not a simple trading network. It passed through thousands of citied and towns. It started from eastern China, across Central Asia and the Middle East, and ended in the Mediterranean Sea. It was used from about 200 B, C, to about A, D, 1300, when sea travel offered new routes , It was sometimes called the world's longest highway. However, the Silk Road was made up of many routes, not one smooth path. They passed through what are now 18 countries. The routes crossed mountains and deserts and had many dangers of hot sun, deep snow and even battles. Only experie...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Silk Road ; Past and Present", "The Silk Road; East Meets West", "The Silk Road; Routes Full of Dangers", "The Silk Road; Pathways for Learning"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1236, "question": "Joan, super visor of the town's morals recently accused George, a local man, of having a drinking problem because she noticed his car outside the town's only bar.She reasoned, it was a logical assumption .George stared at her for a moment and said nothing.Later that evening, he parked his car in front of her house and left it there all night. Why is it that so many of our logical assumptions are just plain wrong? And why do we want to act as if they must be true? In an age long before the Internet, a young American at a party found himself seated next to the famous Chinese diplomat Wellington Koo.Completely not knowing what to say to someone from such a different culture, this young man turned and asked, \"Likee soupee?\" After all, he assumed, don't all Chinese speak in broken English? Mr.K...\n\nQ: How is this passage mainly developed?", "options": ["By giving examples.", "By presenting research results.", "By analyzing causes.", "By making comparisons."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 898, "question": "Do you want to write your password down so that no one can see it, or do you want to send someone a secret message? Knowing how to make an invisible ink message will have you feeling like a secret agent in no time. These are instructions for making invisible ink using baking soda. Difficulty: Easy Time required: A few minutes What you need: Baking soda, Paper, Water, Light bulb, Paintbrush, Measuring cup, Purple grape juice Here's how: There are at least two methods of using baking soda as invisible ink. Mix equal amounts of water and baking soda. Use a paintbrush to write a message onto white paper, using the baking soda solution as \"ink\". Allow the ink to dry. One way to read the message is to hold the paper up to a heat source, such as a light bulb. The baking soda will cause the writin...\n\nQ: From the process, we can know that making invisible ink is_.", "options": ["very hard", "not difficult", "a little difficult", "not easy"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1042, "question": "Children will find it more difficult to buy cigarettes as vending machines selling tobacco will be officially banned in England today.According to the British Heart Foundation(BHF),around 200,000 young people start smoking regularly in England each year and 11 per cent of l1-to15-year-old regular smokers in England and Wales get their cigarettes from vending machines. Betty McBride, Director of Policy and Communications at the British Heart Foundation,said,\"Thousands of children who are at risk of addiction regularly get tobacco from these machines,which of course,don't ask them to prove their age.With the tobacco industry increasingly depending on young smokers to keep their profits,they're fighting tooth and nail to stop any changes that might hit their bottom line.\" The ban, which makes...\n\nQ: According to the text,vending machines selling cigarettes  _  .", "options": ["offer cheaper products", "have more varieties of products", "don't check buyers' personal information", "keep a record of every purchase"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 528, "question": "Are you having too much salt? You might not think so, but people in China eat on average about 12 grams of salt each day, that is much higher than the 6 grams suggested by the World Health Organization. You could be eating too much without realizing it, because about 75% of the salt we eat is already in the food we buy, such as bread, sauces, soups and sausages. What problems can eating too much salt cause? To answer that question, first let's take a look at what salt is. Salt is a chemical compound. It is made of sodium and chloride . Salt is used to keep and flavor foods. A small amount of salt is important for good health because our bodies need sodium and chloride to work. But past studies have found that people who eat more salt than they need tend to have high blood pressure. Eating ...\n\nQ: For a healthier life, the author's suggestion is to   _  .", "options": ["cut back on food with less salt", "eat less heavily salted food", "eat as much reduced salt bread as is wanted", "stop eating bread and breakfast cereals"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 74, "question": "Some people collect stamps. Other people collect works of art or musical instruments. But a man in the American state of Maryland collects secrets. For the past 10 years, people have been sending Frank Warren postcards and other objects with secrets written on them. He now has a million secrets. \"It's a drawing of a lift. And the secret says: 'I feel guilty when I take lifts for one floor, so I limp when I get out.'\" Frank said. Ten years ago, Mr. Warren created an art project called PostSecret. People then began to send him postcards, other objects and emails telling their secrets. Every Sunday, he chooses 10 secrets and puts them on the website. Mr. Warren says he created PostSecret so people could share their secrets in a safe place. \"I was struggling with secrets in my own life. And it...\n\nQ: Mr. Warren created PostSecret in order to   _  .", "options": ["satisfy his curiosity about others' secrets", "collect more materials for his series of books", "offer a safe place for people to share their secrets", "earn a lot of money by sharing others' secrets online"], "answer": 2}]